Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Technical Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Integrated Technical Services and Systems records of Donald Waters, 1986-1994; Accession 1995-A-067a
  - Yale University (Box 7)
    - Financial Administration Group (Box 7)
  - Yale University Library (Box 7)
    - Five Year Plan (Box 7)
    - Lewis Walpole Library (Box 7)
    - Preservation Task Force, Final Report, 1986 May (Box 7)
    - Promotion Review (Box 7)
    - Reorganization (Box 7)
    - SCOPA Forum, 1993 December (Box 7)
  - Computer files, 412 (Box 8–13)
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
    - TECH SERVICES FORMS, 1995-a-067-0001; 1 (Box 8)
    - RLG STATS, 1995-a-067-0002; 1 (Box 8)
    - C&T Time Records 93-94 (Lous files for beg. or the fiscal yr. only. This info is duplicated on the Excel disk.), 1995-a-067-0003; 1 (Box 8)
    - C&T 92-93, 1995-a-067-0004; 1 (Box 8)
    - Preparations Support, Statistics 1993-1994, 1995-a-067-0005; 1 (Box 8)
    - M&P Time Lost, 92-93, 1995-a-067-0006; 1 (Box 8)
    - C&T Time reports, Fiscal 89/90, 1995-a-067-0007; 1 (Box 8)
    - Students 2-24-90, thru 4-28-90, 4-23-89 - 2-17-90, 1995-a-067-0008; 1 (Box 8)
    - HMS Documents, (IBM), 1995-a-067-0009; 1 (Box 8)
    - Serials Recon, Project Statistics, Lotus 1,2,3., 1995-a-067-0010; 1 (Box 8)
    - Monograph Team, Statistics, 92-93, 1995-a-067-0011; 1 (Box 8)
    - Authorities, 92/93, 1995-a-067-0012; 1 (Box 8)
    - Serials Statistics, 92-93, 1995-a-067-0013; 1 (Box 8)
    - Students, 92-93, 1995-a-067-0014; 1 (Box 8)
    - Recon Stats - Word Perfect, 91-92, 92-93, 1995-a-067-0015; 1 (Box 8)
    - Order Support Team, Statistics, 92-93, 1995-a-067-0016; 1 (Box 8)
    - Fiscal Support, Statistics, 92-, 1995-a-067-0017; 1 (Box 8)
    - Preparations Support, 1992/1993, 1995-a-067-0018; 1 (Box 8)
    - C&T Time, 91/92, 1995-a-067-0019; 1 (Box 8)
    - Authorities, 91-92, 1995-a-067-0020; 1 (Box 8)
    - C&T Time 90/91, 1995-a-067-0021; 1 (Box 8)
    - (includes averages), Individual + Team, Cataloging Stats, 94/95, Disk One, July 94 - Dec 94, 1995-a-067-0022; 1 (Box 8)
    - Cataloging Statistics, 1995-a-067-0023; 1 (Box 8)
    - Authorities, 95/96, 1995-a-067-0024; 1 (Box 8)
    - Individual + Team, Cataloging Stats, 94/95, Disk Two, January 95 - June 95, 1995-a-067-0025; 1 (Box 8)
    - Cataloging Statistics, for MLM 93-94, Excel 3.0, 1995-a-067-0026; 1 (Box 8)
    - Authorities 93-94, Excel 3.0, 1995-a-067-0027; 1 (Box 8)
    - Monograph Cataloging, Activity Stas, 93/94, Excel 4.0, 2/94, 1995-a-067-0028; 1 (Box 8)
    - Authorities Statistics, FY 94/95, 1995-a-067-0029; 1 (Box 8)
    - Cataloging Stats, (Excel), 1995-a-067-0030; 1 (Box 8)
    - C&T 93-94 Excel Files, Other (not Acquisitions), 1995-a-067-0031; 1 (Box 8)
    - WP Clipart, 1995-a-067-0032; 1 (Box 8)
    - Orbis Costs, 7/93 - 8/93, 1995-a-067-0033; 1 (Box 8)
    - Orbis Costs 1/93 - 2/93, 1995-a-067-0034; 1 (Box 8)
    - Orbis Costs 5/93 - 6/93, 1995-a-067-0035; 1 (Box 8)
    - Word Clipart, 1995-a-067-0036; 1 (Box 8)
    - Email:, Aug 95, Sept 95, 1995-a-067-0037; 1 (Box 8)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0038; 1 (Box 8)
    - Mercury Icon, 1995-a-067-0039; 1 (Box 8)
    - #22, 1995-a-067-0040; 1 (Box 8)
    - High Density, Barbs machine only, 1995-a-067-0041; 1 (Box 8)
    - Student Revised, 90-91, 1995-a-067-0042; 1 (Box 8)
    - Authority Stats, 89/90, 1995-a-067-0043; 1 (Box 8)
    - M&P Time Records, 91/92, 1995-a-067-0044; 1 (Box 8)
    - Project Statistics, Red, green..., 1995-a-067-0045; 1 (Box 8)
    - M&P Time Records, 90/91, 1995-a-067-0046; 1 (Box 8)
    - M&P Time Lost records, 89/90, 1995-a-067-0047; 1 (Box 8)
    - Backup 3/2/92, PDOX 3/Backup, Catmerge 6-18-92, 1995-a-067-0048; 1 (Box 8)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0049; 1 (Box 8)
    - Students 91-92, disk #1, July 1 - Apr 18, 1992, 1995-a-067-0050; 1 (Box 8)
    - Authorities 90/91, 1995-a-067-0051; 1 (Box 8)
    - Students 91/92, disk #2, 4/25 - 6/92, 1995-a-067-0052; 1 (Box 8)
    - Fiscal Support, Statistics 96-97, 1995-a-067-0053; 1 (Box 8)
    - Fiscal Support Statistics FY 1994-1995, Excel 4.0, Mac., 1995-a-067-0054; 1 (Box 8)
    - Microtext Labels, 1995-a-067-0055; 1 (Box 8)
    - Monograph Cataloging Activity, FY 94/95, 1995-a-067-0056; 1 (Box 8)
    - Orbis Costs 9/93 - 10/93, 1995-a-067-0057; 1 (Box 8)
    - Orbis Costs, 3/93 + 4/93, 1995-a-067-0058; 1 (Box 8)
    - Statistics Templates, 95/96, 1995-a-067-0059; 1 (Box 8)
    - Serial Support Stats, FY 1994/1995, Excel 4.0, Mac, 1995-a-067-0060; 1 (Box 8)
    - Cataloging, Stats, Proc Services, 1995/1996, 1995-a-067-0061; 1 (Box 8)
    - Student Wages, 1995/1996, 1995-a-067-0062; 1 (Box 8)
    - Acq Stats, 1995/1996, 1995-a-067-0063; 1 (Box 8)
    - Student Wages, 1995/1996, 1995-a-067-0064; 1 (Box 8)
    - Norton Disk Doctor/UnErase, 1995-a-067-0065; 1 (Box 8)
    - Roper Fin, (wp6.0), 1995-a-067-0066; 1 (Box 8)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0067; 1 (Box 8)
    - Quickmail stuff saved from Mac, 1995-a-067-0068; 1 (Box 8)
    - Orbis Budget, 1995-a-067-0069; 1 (Box 8)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0070; 1 (Box 8)
    - OCLC, 1995-a-067-0071; 1 (Box 8)
    - Student Payroll Template, 96/97, Acq. + Cat., 1995-a-067-0072; 1 (Box 9)
    - Orbis Budget Stuff, 1995-a-067-0073; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0074; 1 (Box 9)
    - PC/MAC, Excel + Word Files, 1995-a-067-0075; 1 (Box 9)
    - Monograph Support, Statistics 96-97, 1995-a-067-0076; 1 (Box 9)
    - Orders Support, Statistics 96-97, 1995-a-067-0077; 1 (Box 9)
    - Click Here, 1995-a-067-0078; 1 (Box 9)
    - Click Here, 1995-a-067-0079; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0080; 1 (Box 9)
    - lmc web page docs, 1995-a-067-0081; 1 (Box 9)
    - Misc, 1995-a-067-0082; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0083; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0084; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0085; 1 (Box 9)
    - Meeting Maker XP2.1, 1995-a-067-0086; 1 (Box 9)
    - 10/95, Email, 10/95, 1995-a-067-0087; 1 (Box 9)
    - E-Mail, 11/95 - 12/95, 1995-a-067-0088; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0089; 1 (Box 9)
    - INPII.PDF, (Formatted for PC), 1995-a-067-0090; 1 (Box 9)
    - INPII.DOC, Word 6.0, (Formated for Mac), 1995-a-067-0091; 1 (Box 9)
    - BLK III FY 96, GA 816A 819A, 1995-a-067-0092; 1 (Box 9)
    - Wages '96, 1995-a-067-0093; 1 (Box 9)
    - Desktop Textures, 1995-a-067-0094; 1 (Box 9)
    - E-mail, 4/95 - 5/95;, 7/95;, Mtg Maker, 1995-a-067-0095; 1 (Box 9)
    - Adobe Acrobat File:, DATFMERG.PDF, 1995-a-067-0096; 1 (Box 9)
    - Monograph Support Stats, FY 1994-1995, Excel 4.0, 1995-a-067-0097; 1 (Box 9)
    - Order Support, FY 94/95, Statistics, 1995-a-067-0098; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0099; 1 (Box 9)
    - FY 1994-1995, Serials Recon, Statistics, Excel 4.0, 1995-a-067-0100; 1 (Box 9)
    - Recon Statistics, for Rare Book Team, FY 93/94 + 94/95, 1995-a-067-0101; 1 (Box 9)
    - Student Time Records, FY 94-95, Excel 4.0, 1995-a-067-0102; 1 (Box 9)
    - Administrative Assistant Manual, 1995-a-067-0103; 1 (Box 9)
    - Template, 3.0, 2.2, 1995-a-067-0104; 1 (Box 9)
    - Lotus 123 R3 +, Paradox R 35, Files, 1995-a-067-0105; 1 (Box 9)
    - Excel, Cat Costs, 1995-a-067-0106; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0107; 1 (Box 9)
    - WP51\Barb\**, -Stef\**, \moc\**, 1995-a-067-0108; 1 (Box 9)
    - WP 5.1, Docs + Labels 12/94, WP 5.1, from PC, \Docs; \Moc, 1995-a-067-0109; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0110; 1 (Box 9)
    - SML Staff, 1995-a-067-0111; 1 (Box 9)
    - Backup #1, 11/22/95, 1995-a-067-0112; 1 (Box 9)
    - #2, 1995-a-067-0113; 1 (Box 9)
    - #3, 1995-a-067-0114; 1 (Box 9)
    - #4, 1995-a-067-0115; 1 (Box 9)
    - #5, 1995-a-067-0116; 1 (Box 9)
    - #6, 1995-a-067-0117; 1 (Box 9)
    - #7, 1995-a-067-0118; 1 (Box 9)
    - #8, 1995-a-067-0119; 1 (Box 9)
    - #9, 1995-a-067-0120; 1 (Box 9)
    - #10, 1995-a-067-0121; 1 (Box 9)
    - #11, 1995-a-067-0122; 1 (Box 9)
    - #12, 1995-a-067-0123; 1 (Box 9)
    - #13, 1995-a-067-0124; 1 (Box 9)
    - #14, 1995-a-067-0125; 1 (Box 9)
    - #15, 1995-a-067-0126; 1 (Box 9)
    - #16, 1995-a-067-0127; 1 (Box 9)
    - #17, 1995-a-067-0128; 1 (Box 9)
    - #18, 1995-a-067-0129; 1 (Box 9)
    - #19, 1995-a-067-0130; 1 (Box 9)
    - #20, 1995-a-067-0131; 1 (Box 9)
    - #21, 1995-a-067-0132; 1 (Box 9)
    - #23, 1995-a-067-0133; 1 (Box 9)
    - #24, 1995-a-067-0134; 1 (Box 9)
    - #25, 1995-a-067-0135; 1 (Box 9)
    - #26, 1995-a-067-0136; 1 (Box 9)
    - #27, 1995-a-067-0137; 1 (Box 9)
    - #28, 1995-a-067-0138; 1 (Box 9)
    - #29, 1995-a-067-0139; 1 (Box 9)
    - #30, 1995-a-067-0140; 1 (Box 9)
    - Students Time Records, 93-94, (through 8/23/93), WordPerfect, 1995-a-067-0141; 1 (Box 9)
    - E-mail Folders + Files, 6/94 - 8/94, 1995-a-067-0142; 1 (Box 9)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0143; 1 (Box 9)
    - E-mail Folders, 11/94 -> Received Mail, 1995-a-067-0144; 1 (Box 10)
    - November 1994, YULIBL, 1995-a-067-0145; 1 (Box 10)
    - YULIB-L, December 1994, 1995-a-067-0146; 1 (Box 10)
    - Word Back-Up, 11/94 4, 1995-a-067-0147; 1 (Box 10)
    - Word Back-Up, 11/94 3, 1995-a-067-0148; 1 (Box 10)
    - Word Back-Up, 11/94 2, 1995-a-067-0149; 1 (Box 10)
    - Word Back-Up, 11/94 1, 1995-a-067-0150; 1 (Box 10)
    - Excel Back-Up, 11/94 - 2, 1995-a-067-0151; 1 (Box 10)
    - Excel Back-Up (workshts), 11/94, 1995-a-067-0152; 1 (Box 10)
    - Social Science, Retreat, 3/94, 1995-a-067-0153; 1 (Box 10)
    - Email Relating to, Soc Sci + Systems, Searches, 1995-a-067-0154; 1 (Box 10)
    - Labels, Word 5., 11/93, 1995-a-067-0155; 1 (Box 10)
    - E-mail Folders + Files, 9/94 - 10/94, Some 11/94 also, 1995-a-067-0156; 1 (Box 10)
    - YULIB-L, August 94, 1995-a-067-0157; 1 (Box 10)
    - YULIB-L, September 1994, October 1994, 1995-a-067-0158; 1 (Box 10)
    - YULIB-L, May 1994 thru July 1994, 1995-a-067-0159; 1 (Box 10)
    - JMS E-Mail, 7/94, 1995-a-067-0160; 1 (Box 10)
    - Kusack Spring 94, 1995-a-067-0161; 1 (Box 10)
    - YULIB-L, February 1994, +, March 1994, 1995-a-067-0162; 1 (Box 10)
    - YULIB-L, April 1994, 1995-a-067-0163; 1 (Box 10)
    - Wages Mac, 1995-a-067-0164; 1 (Box 10)
    - File Indices 12/94, 1995-a-067-0165; 1 (Box 10)
    - March 1995, Email, 1995-a-067-0166; 1 (Box 10)
    - Jan+Feb 95, Email Folders, 1995-a-067-0167; 1 (Box 10)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0168; 1 (Box 10)
    - December 1994 E-mail, 1995-a-067-0169; 1 (Box 10)
    - Fiscal Support Statistics, 1993-1994, Excel 3.0, 1995-a-067-0170; 1 (Box 10)
    - Disinfectant Program, 1995-a-067-0171; 1 (Box 10)
    - Judy 1/96, 1995-a-067-0172; 1 (Box 10)
    - Students Time Records, 93-94, (beginning 9/4/93), Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel 5/94-6/94, 1995-a-067-0173; 1 (Box 10)
    - Preservation, C+T FY '93-94, 1995-a-067-0174; 1 (Box 10)
    - C+T 93-94 Excel Files, Acquisitions, 1995-a-067-0175; 1 (Box 10)
    - M&P Time Records 93-94, Excel Files, 1995-a-067-0176; 1 (Box 10)
    - MS Word documents, 1995-a-067-0177; 1 (Box 10)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0178; 1 (Box 10)
    - Serial Support Statistics, 1993/1994, Excel 3.0, 1995-a-067-0179; 1 (Box 10)
    - Order Support Stats, 1995-a-067-0180; 1 (Box 10)
    - Monograph Support 93-94, 1995-a-067-0181; 1 (Box 10)
    - Serials Recon Project, Statistics 93-94, Excel, 1995-a-067-0182; 1 (Box 10)
    - E-Mail Folders + Files, 10/93 - 2/94, 1995-a-067-0183; 1 (Box 10)
    - Blank-formatted, E-mail 2/94 - 5/94, 1995-a-067-0184; 1 (Box 10)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0185; 1 (Box 10)
    - JDR3LST.91 JDR3S.92, JDR3LET.91, JDR 1993, JDR3-91, JDR1994, 1994mini.yes, 1995-a-067-0201; 1 (Box 10)
    - Nakajima (6) JGS, Brellster Fund, 6.23SAAR.IO, GHATALK, BFMTG.SUM, 1995-a-067-0202; 1 (Box 10)
    - Working Paper Covers Only, 11-01-96, WP#236, 1995-a-067-0203; 1 (Box 10)
    - SkimonKar.Aug, 1995-a-067-0204; 1 (Box 10)
    - BHG/Bio/C.V., meetings, Voluntas conf., 11/95, 1995-a-067-0205; 1 (Box 10)
    - 3/20/1992, Letter re ARNOVA, meeting to --- alumni, 1995-a-067-0206; 1 (Box 10)
    - Elodie Colette's work/research, (formated for mac), 1995-a-067-0207; 1 (Box 10)
    - BHG, 1995-a-067-0208; 1 (Box 10)
    - Brewfund, Brewster.mag, magat.brw, 1995-a-067-0209; 1 (Box 10)
    - Religion Project:, Black Churches in N.H., Lewis Gordon/David Williams, 1995-a-067-0210; 1 (Box 10)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0211; 1 (Box 10)
    - WN data for school, All data, 1995-a-067-0212; 1 (Box 10)
    - Transfers: Terry + Pam, David Williams Project, letter + mailing addresses, 1995-a-067-0213; 1 (Box 10)
    - Carson-menu, 1995-a-067-0214; 1 (Box 10)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0215; 1 (Box 10)
    - Lilly, Red, Rep, 1995-a-067-0216; 1 (Box 10)
    - Arnova paper, Brad, Yamada, Grayberg.rev, 11.2.92, 1995-a-067-0217; 1 (Box 10)
    - Tufts Ellas Advcom.let, Luciano FordProg Shin, Hewlett.92, Proposal Japan3.PRO, 1.15.92, Taxonomy, Haruo, Japan.LST, Japan.LAB, 1995-a-067-0218; 1 (Box 10)
    - Terry Schmidt, YPB info 1, 1995-a-067-0219; 1 (Box 10)
    - Religion project, -Powell talk transcript, pp 87-134, 1995-a-067-0220; 1 (Box 10)
    - Evaluation Questions, 1995-a-067-0221; 1 (Box 10)
    - Terry Schmidt YPB info 1, Yale Macintosh Users' Group, 1995-a-067-0222; 1 (Box 10)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0223; 1 (Box 10)
    - TDAT2.DAT, 1995-a-067-0224; 1 (Box 10)
    - TDAT1b.dat, 1995-a-067-0225; 1 (Box 10)
    - TDAT1a.dat, 1995-a-067-0226; 1 (Box 10)
    - HA Paper.2, Voluntas.tlk, Hmoproj.rev, RWJ-12-16-92, 1995-a-067-0227; 1 (Box 10)
    - BHF, Res rps, Drafts, 1995-a-067-0228; 1 (Box 10)
    - CH9BG Ch10B6, GRAY10 Tab611.3, GRAY11 NHFound, 9.16Orig, 1995-a-067-0229; 1 (Box 10)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0230; 1 (Box 10)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0231; 1 (Box 10)
    - MS Word S.1 Back-up Install Backup Eudora "Out", 1995-a-067-0232; 1 (Box 11)
    - #5, 1995-a-067-0233; 1 (Box 11)
    - Brewfund, Brewster.mag, magat.brw, 1995-a-067-0234; 1 (Box 11)
    - Ponpo Resource Center, 1995-a-067-0235; 1 (Box 11)
    - Japan3.Pro, JapanGa.Has IBM, INTRO.ARN, RHYSW.WSI, Japan Grant, JapanGRA.2, JapanGRA.WPS, 1995-a-067-0236; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0237; 1 (Box 11)
    - FundRais, 1995-a-067-0238; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0239; 1 (Box 11)
    - Brewfund, 1995-a-067-0240; 1 (Box 11)
    - CV.BHG, 1995-a-067-0241; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0242; 1 (Box 11)
    - Keio Proposal Shimada.Oct Planning.Pro Ishida.Jun Landy Shimada.3 MC.LET, 1995-a-067-0243; 1 (Box 11)
    - BrianO, LLAB, 1995-a-067-0244; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0245; 1 (Box 11)
    - Budget, Election, Election.cos, 1995-a-067-0246; 1 (Box 11)
    - 1-2-92, Res rep - B6, 3-19 Benno, Progress Bio+Let, Newsletter piece: file: GRAY.2, Taping 9.31 Proposal.url, 1995-a-067-0247; 1 (Box 11)
    - Gray2.DN, Gray5.DN, DRTAB2.1, Chapterl.wp, GR3FUT, GR3FUT.TAB, GRAY3.DN, GRNT7, 1995-a-067-0248; 1 (Box 11)
    - Circa '98, Budget info, 1995-a-067-0249; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0250; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0251; 1 (Box 11)
    - Arqioua Boors, 3/2/93 - Letter to Publishers, 1995-a-067-0252; 1 (Box 11)
    - Backup, A-E-mail, 1995-a-067-0253; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0254; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0255; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0256; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0257; 1 (Box 11)
    - 1cm paper, Tables1.all, Abzug, Advice, Annrept.Pn, Aspen Tables, 1995-a-067-0260; 1 (Box 11)
    - HMOPROS.REV, GRAY 12.30.92, HMOPROS.793, HAPAPER1.2, HAPAPER.2, 1995-a-067-0261; 1 (Box 11)
    - SEM-ANMT, YAMADA, SWEDENIK, 1995-a-067-0262; 1 (Box 11)
    - Peter Hall AHC Talk, Shimada Orosz, Proposal.REV Gross, Ind Hasting MC. LET, Sindelar Survey, Foster AAPAPER, 1995-a-067-0263; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0264; 1 (Box 11)
    - Proposal to the Rockefeller Family & Assoc. for the JDR III Program (4/94), 1995-a-067-0265; 1 (Box 11)
    - Peter's copy of LIST, "List-PDH.doc", 1995-a-067-0266; 1 (Box 11)
    - National Seminar 3/2000 Notes, 1995-a-067-0267; 1 (Box 11)
    - National Seminar 3/2000, 1995-a-067-0268; 1 (Box 11)
    - Press Releases, Theological Principles, To R. Parrot, 1995-a-067-0269; 1 (Box 11)
    - Web Page, 1995-a-067-0270; 1 (Box 11)
    - National Seminar, Oct. Mtg 1999, 1995-a-067-0271; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0272; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0273; 1 (Box 11)
    - Religion Sem. lists, Ponpo Sem. lists, Kellogg, 1995-a-067-0274; 1 (Box 11)
    - NPO Mission Statements, 1995-a-067-0275; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0276; 1 (Box 11)
    - Agenda 1099, 1995-a-067-0277; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0278; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0279; 1 (Box 11)
    - Ponpo, Publication - GMM, 6-20-95, 1995-a-067-0280; 1 (Box 11)
    - Cases in Nonprofit Governance, CIVG-LTST, CIVGCVR'S, Religion Seminar List, 1995-a-067-0281; 1 (Box 11)
    - Alu9423AB -Divinity School, 1.1974-118, 2.1979-131, 3.1984-18, 4.1989-151, 5.1992-106, 6.1994-134, 7.1996-139, 8.1998-93, merged list, purged list, Excel, 1995-a-067-0282; 1 (Box 11)
    - Alumni Careers Survey, Alumni letters, Survey Form, Post card followup, 1995-a-067-0283; 1 (Box 11)
    - Working Paper List, 1995-a-067-0284; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0285; 1 (Box 11)
    - Annual report, 1999-2000, 1995-a-067-0286; 1 (Box 11)
    - Lilly, Leadership, Workshops, 1995-a-067-0287; 1 (Box 11)
    - Purged List, Data Entry - survey alumni, 1995-a-067-0288; 1 (Box 11)
    - Kellogg Transcripts - May 99, 1995-a-067-0289; 1 (Box 11)
    - Lilly Leadership Final, Financial Report, 1995-a-067-0290; 1 (Box 11)
    - Lilly Leadership, Grant Acctg, 1995-a-067-0291; 1 (Box 11)
    - Lilly Polity Grant Acctg., Mar '98 -> Present, Lilly Polity 1998 Report, 1995-a-067-0292; 1 (Box 11)
    - Aspen/Ford, 1995-a-067-0293; 1 (Box 11)
    - Nathan Cummings, List, (use for back-up only), 1995-a-067-0294; 1 (Box 11)
    - NUSQ, 1995-a-067-0295; 1 (Box 11)
    - Religion Project, Seminar Transcripts, June 13-14, 1991, 1995-a-067-0296; 1 (Box 11)
    - Milossky, 1995-a-067-0297; 1 (Box 11)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0298; 1 (Box 11)
    - Trustee.Da, #Rec. = 6115, 5/17/93, 1995-a-067-0299; 1 (Box 11)
    - Mailing Lists/Labels, 1995-a-067-0300; 1 (Box 11)
    - Trusteeship, Back up II, Complete Article List, as of 6/17/93, 1995-a-067-0301; 1 (Box 11)
    - Trusteeship Project, Back up Disk - Pam, 1995-a-067-0302; 1 (Box 11)
    - Trusteeship Articles, Reader's Guide to Periodical Literature, 1900-1980, 1995-a-067-0303; 1 (Box 11)
    - Rhys Williams Interview with James Dittes, 1995-a-067-0304; 1 (Box 11)
    - 1995 Japan List, 1995 Annual Report Codemail, Yalelist, 2codeyale, smlst, 1995-a-067-0305; 1 (Box 11)
    - Ponpo update - Georgeanne's disk, 1995-a-067-0306; 1 (Box 11)
    - Gray2.wp Graynot2.wp, Gray3.wp Graynot3.wp, Gray4.wp Graynot4.wp, 1995-a-067-0307; 1 (Box 11)
    - 55060-10.cal, Hewlet.wk1, Hewnew.wki, Kate 9-20-90, NSHEWLET.WK1, 1995-a-067-0308; 1 (Box 12)
    - Pam's Update Files, 1995-a-067-0309; 1 (Box 12)
    - Letters by Karen, 1995-a-067-0310; 1 (Box 12)
    - Printer Use Only, 1995-a-067-0311; 1 (Box 12)
    - Pam - Back up, General Office/Special Projects, 1995-a-067-0312; 1 (Box 12)
    - Terry-, Copy of Diskette from Peter:, Law Review - Religion, 1995-a-067-0313; 1 (Box 12)
    - Religion Project, Rhys Williams, Religion Files, 7/28/13, 1995-a-067-0314; 1 (Box 12)
    - Religion Project, Back up Disk II, 1995-a-067-0315; 1 (Box 12)
    - Religious Project, Back up Disk - Pam, Letters & Memos, 1991-1992, 1995-a-067-0316; 1 (Box 12)
    - SocioFile, 1/74-12/90, 1995-a-067-0317; 1 (Box 12)
    - Trusteeship Articles Files, Bibliography, Religion Articles Files, 1995-a-067-0318; 1 (Box 12)
    - Prinlei use Only, 1995-a-067-0319; 1 (Box 12)
    - Anti-Virus (Boot Sector) Rescue Disk, (1) Put in Drive A, (2) Reboot, (3) Type RESCUE, (4) Select "Restore" Option, 1995-a-067-0320; 1 (Box 12)
    - Lisa Prog 95, 1995-a-067-0321; 1 (Box 12)
    - 1996-97, Ponpo.seminars, Religion.seminars, Kellog, lillypol.wp5, 1995-a-067-0322; 1 (Box 12)
    - Don Green Karen, Judith Goldstein, 1995-a-067-0323; 1 (Box 12)
    - 2/24 Panel Flier, Name Cds - LL wkshp,, Connecting Strategies Proposal, 1995-a-067-0324; 1 (Box 12)
    - bios - LRB, 1995-a-067-0325; 1 (Box 12)
    - Notes from Oct. 15, 16, National Seminar, Alexandria, VA, 1995-a-067-0326; 1 (Box 12)
    - Computer Back-ups:, Peter's Schedule, Peter's Messages, Peter - Personal, 1995-a-067-0327; 1 (Box 12)
    - "Sacred Companies" Syllabus, 1995-a-067-0328; 1 (Box 12)
    - National Seminar, January 199, 1995-a-067-0329; 1 (Box 12)
    - biopcr.m99, 1995-a-067-0330; 1 (Box 12)
    - Ponpo, Working Papers, Orders, 1995-a-067-0331; 1 (Box 12)
    - Ponpo Mail List, Publication List GMM, 6-30-94, 1995-a-067-0332; 1 (Box 12)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0333; 1 (Box 12)
    - Ponpo Mail List, ISPS Seminar Lists, Publication.new, 6-30-95, 1995-a-067-0334; 1 (Box 12)
    - Peter Dobkin Hall 1997, Letters of Rec 1998, bookstore leter, triage, winks, Arnova.pdh, 1995-a-067-0335; 1 (Box 12)
    - Monthly Reports, 1995-a-067-0336; 1 (Box 12)
    - 1995 JDR3, 1996 JDR3, 1997 JDR3, 1998 JDR3, 1995-a-067-0337; 1 (Box 12)
    - Ponpo, EPE 1997, 1995-a-067-0338; 1 (Box 12)
    - religion e-mail list, 1995-a-067-0339; 1 (Box 12)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0340; 1 (Box 12)
    - Seminar Lists Cummings, Ponpo Seminar Lists, 1995-a-067-0341; 1 (Box 12)
    - Seminar Lists, Mailing, Cummings, Value Visions List, 1995-a-067-0342; 1 (Box 12)
    - Seminar Lists, Ponpo, 1995-a-067-0343; 1 (Box 12)
    - Seminar Lists, Ponpo 4, 1995-a-067-0344; 1 (Box 12)
    - Lilly Polity (incl. natl seminar), Visiting Fellows, Bond - July, Fax Template, Telephone List, 1995-a-067-0345; 1 (Box 12)
    - Lilly Polity, 1995-a-067-0346; 1 (Box 12)
    - Lilly polity Grant Accounting, 1998-2000, 1995-a-067-0347; 1 (Box 12)
    - Gift Accounts, 1995-a-067-0348; 1 (Box 12)
    - Kellog Grant Accounting, Gift Accounts, 1995-a-067-0349; 1 (Box 12)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0350; 1 (Box 12)
    - Proposed Budgets Ponpo, Workin Papers + classes sold 98' 99, HSUS Publications, Kellogg National Seminar, 1995-a-067-0351; 1 (Box 13)
    - Evelyn Brody, Doug Rae, Eoin O'Sullivan, S.Kasten, Kellogg, 1995-a-067-0352; 1 (Box 13)
    - Kellogg Finan. Rep., 1995-a-067-0353; 1 (Box 13)
    - BIOS, Correspondence, 1995-a-067-0354; 1 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence (2), 1995-a-067-0355; 1 (Box 13)
    - Kelleval 2/14/99, 1995-a-067-0356; 1 (Box 13)
    - Eudora, Back-up "In", 1995-a-067-0357; 1 (Box 13)
    - Kellogg Proposal, Final Draft, 2-2-95, 1995-a-067-0358; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0359; 1 (Box 13)
    - Perron Papers, 1995-a-067-0360; 1 (Box 13)
    - Pier's Final Report, Jan-June, 2000, Kellogg + Other, 1995-a-067-0361; 1 (Box 13)
    - [no label information], 1995-a-067-0362; 1 (Box 13)
    - Download Bios, 1995-a-067-0363; 1 (Box 13)
    - Backup, E-mail, M-Word, 1995-a-067-0364; 1 (Box 13)
    - W-Wood to Ponpo, Sem List, 1995-a-067-0365; 1 (Box 13)
    - E-Mail-MWood, 1995-a-067-0366; 1 (Box 13)